{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Vinyl \u0026 PVC Fence Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40255/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40255,"taskName":"Vinyl or PVC Fence - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Partially Replace a PVC or Plastic Fence","xmTaskDescriptor":"Vinyl \u0026 PVC Fence Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":379,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"FENCES Vinyl fencing PVC picket","textMessagingName":"Repr PVC Fence","rolloverLongDesc":"Sometimes made with wood or metal reinforcements in the posts or cross-members. Usually looks just like wooden fences or metal fences but requires little or no maintenance.","rolloverShortDesc":"Typically made of PVC but looks like metal or wood.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Partially Replace a PVC or Plastic Fence.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Vinyl Fence Repair Companies | Fix PVC Fencing","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":30,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Vinyl or PVC Fence Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Vinyl or PVC Fence - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Vinyl or PVC Fence Project","urlName":"Vinyl-or-PVC-Fence-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Vinyl Fence Repair Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | PVC Fencing","searchKeywords":"FENCES,Vinyl,fencing,PVC,picket,privacy,,yard,white,pipe","emcCategoryOid":-12030,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":562,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40255/":{"taskOID":40255,"originalTaskOID":40255,"setID":562,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4176,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Repair Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the kind(s) of repair you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4823,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Post is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Post is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4824,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Post is wobbly","answerDisplayText":"Post is wobbly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2408,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fence is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Fence is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2410,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fence is rusty","answerDisplayText":"Fence is rusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fence is loose","answerDisplayText":"Fence is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":856,"questionDisplayText":"Fence height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the height of the fence you want to have repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4176,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Repair Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the kind(s) of repair you need.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4823,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Post is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Post is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4824,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Post is wobbly","answerDisplayText":"Post is wobbly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2408,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fence is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Fence is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2410,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fence is rusty","answerDisplayText":"Fence is rusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fence is loose","answerDisplayText":"Fence is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4823,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Post is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Post is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4824,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Post is wobbly","answerDisplayText":"Post is wobbly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2408,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fence is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Fence is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2410,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fence is rusty","answerDisplayText":"Fence is rusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fence is loose","answerDisplayText":"Fence is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2764,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gate is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Gate is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2922,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","answerDisplayText":"Hardware is damaged/broken/missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":856,"questionDisplayText":"Fence height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the height of the fence you want to have repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}